

Yang, Bo

Developer



+1-415-420-9693



https://yang-bo.com



yang-bo@yang-bo.com



pop_atry



yang_bo



955091



Atry

About me -

I am a developer who knows how to create application frameworks.

I founded a number of open-source projects for creating micro-services, neural networks, reactive GUIs, and DSLs, which are stared 3000+ times on GitHub.

My current interests include machine learning infrastructure and the application of functional programming languages to real-world problems.

Skills -

Scala

Machine Learning

Software Design

Agile Project Management

Hack *5.5 Haxe *5.5 OpenCL *5 DevOps *5 ActionScript *4 C++ *4 Java *4 JavaScript *4 Rust *4 OCaml *4 Testing *3 C *3 Spark *3 Akka *3

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Experience

2023-	Preemo Inc Machine I As Preemo's only MLE, I conceptualized and solely implement nancy service for fine-tune and infererence from scratch. Preemonths://gradient.ai is a wrapper of the service I built.	
2019-2022	Meta Platforms Inc I built machine learning infrastructure to detect payment fraud and a variety of products. Then I joined the Hack/HHVM OSS team, whe of maintaining HHVM's open-source branch.	
2015-2019	Thoughtworks Inc Senior Consultant, I maintained a number of open-source projects sponsored by Thoug Tech Lead, delivered various projects of mobile, web applications, an	htWorks, and as a
2014	Shenzhen QiFun Network Corp., LTD I led the Q-Force Team in developing a game engine along with its two mobile games.	Tech Lead related tools, and
2011-2013	Shenzhen Putaoteng Network Technology Co., Ltd. I led the start-up team in developing a 3D side-scrolling game engin social game Nan Da Nu Pei.	Co-founder e VinyHome and a
2008-2011	NetEase, Inc. I participated in various product teams as a developer or the techning Zhan Guo Feng Yun (web game), Ka Pai Dui Jue (web game), De engine).	
2007	Beijing HiPiHi Information Technology Corp.,Ltd developed in the both server-side and client-side of the 3D virtual was	Software Engineer orld, HiPiHi World.
2006-2007	Beijing AutoNavi Software Co., Ltd. As a developer, I developed some components for a 3D navigation so	Software Engineer oftware.
Open-so	urce projects	
2021-2022	HHVM is Meta's virtual machine to run Hack. I ported the open source by NixOS and created CI pipeline for building, testing, and packaging H	
since 2018	Dsl.scala is a framework to extend Scala language features in libraries. I also pwork to Haskell as Control.Dsl.	Scala ported this frame-
since 2016	DeepLearning.scala and Compute.scala are libraries for creating complex neural networks.	Scala
since 2015	Binding.scala is a reactive templating language for creating web and desktop GUI.	Scala
2015-2016	Microbuilder Haxe / Scala / is a toolkit to build system across micro-services implemented in v communicating via RESTful JSON API.	Java / JavaScript various languages
since 2012	haxe-continuation provides async/await syntax for Haxe.	Haxe
since 2010	protoc-gen-as3 is a Protocol Buffers plugin for ActionScript 3.	ActionScript3
since 2007	other 100+ of open-source projects	
Dulalia ati	iona	
Publicati	IONS	

2017	Mondic Deep Learning	first author
2017	Ad-hoc polymorphic delimited continuations	first author
2009	Adobe Flex 3: Training from the Source	translator
Talks		
2017	Deeplearning.scala - Thoughts and practices on OSS AI framework	DBTC
2017	Ad II D I I	Strange Loop

ArchData Summit · Beijing

QCon · Beijing

ECUG Con

Education

2017

2016

2015

2002-2006 Southwest University of Political Science and Law Bachelor Of Laws

Specific-domain extension in an universal language

Neural Networks & Functional Programming

More than Async